I want you to think back to who you were
when you started this journey in lesson one.
Think about the intention you set
and the goals you articulated.
Now think about where you are today.
The growth that has happened in a season
of focused conditioning is profound.
The best way to solidify that growth
is to review your game tape.
In your playbook, you'll find the final section
of your 90-Day Way scorecard.
It's your personal post-season review.
It's going to prompt you to identify your biggest wins
and your most significant breakthroughs
across each of the A.R.A.W. pillars.
Don't rush this, be specific.
What was your biggest agility win?
Maybe it was a moment you had to pivot on a project
and you did it with confidence.
When did your resilience shine through?
Think of a specific moment you faced criticism
and instead of getting defensive,
you chose to lean in and be curious.
What was your most important alignment breakthrough?
Was there a tough decision you had to make
and you did it because it didn't align with your M.V.P.?
What was your new wellbeing habit?
And maybe how did that make a difference in your energy?
Taking the time to name these wins is not about ego.
It's about encoding the lessons.
When you consciously acknowledge a breakthrough,
you're telling your brain,
this is a new strategy that works, hello.
This is who I am now.
Let's keep it.
You are solidifying the neural pathways
to becoming the athlete you were always meant to be.